{
    "subject": "resource/Barbara_Loden",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/givenName",
    "object": "Barbara",
    "human_readable": "The given name of Barbara Loden is Barbara.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9796691536903381,
            "question": "What is Barbara Loden's given name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9568643569946289,
            "question": "Is 'Barbara' the first name of Barbara Loden?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9466336369514465,
            "question": "Who is Barbara Loden?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9362030625343323,
            "question": "How would you refer to Barbara Loden by her given name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.93025141954422,
            "question": "What is the legal name of Barbara Loden?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9093579649925232,
            "question": "What name was Barbara Loden given at birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.866206169128418,
            "question": "If someone wanted to address Barbara Loden formally, what name should they use?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7997379302978516,
            "question": "Is Barbara a common name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6316624879837036,
            "question": "Can you give me an example of someone else with the name 'Barbara'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.13484768569469452,
            "question": "What is the significance of a person's given name?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The given name of Barbara Loden is Barbara.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2150_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you give me an example of someone else with the name 'Barbara'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2150_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Barbara a common name?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2150_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If someone wanted to address Barbara Loden formally, what name should they use?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2150_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2150_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2150_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2150_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2150_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2150_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2150_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2150_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2150_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2150_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2150_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here's my evaluation:\n\nThe triple to be evaluated is:\n\"The given name of Barbara Loden is Barbara.\"\n\nMy evaluation:\n\n* In file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_2150/re-ranker-msmarco/1.txt, the document mentions \"Barbara Loden (July 8, 1932 \u2013 September 5, 1980)\".\n* In file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_2150/re-ranker-msmarco/6.txt, the document mentions \"Barbara Loden (July 8, 1932 \u2013 September 5, 1980)\".\n* The other documents also consistently use the name \"Barbara Loden\".\n\nTherefore, the information in the documents supports the triple. \n\nThe answer is: \n```\n{\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\nThe documents provide information about Barbara Loden, confirming that her given name is indeed Barbara."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}